[
  {
    "question":"What day of the week doesn't exist?",
    "variants":["Saturday","Wednesday","Holiday","Friday"],
    "currentPrice":"500",
    "answer":"Holiday"
  },
  {
    "question":"How many countries does the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland include?",
    "variants":["8","6","4","2"],
    "currentPrice":"1,000",
    "answer":"4"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which part of speech is possessive in English?",
    "variants":["verb","adjective","adverb","noun"],
    "currentPrice":"2,000",
    "answer":"noun"
  },
  {
    "question":"Which of the following verbs is the king of English verbs?",
    "variants":["to live"," to study"," to have","to be"],
    "currentPrice":"4,000",
    "answer":"to be"
  },
  {
    "question":"How many forms does a verb have in English?",
    "variants":["3","5","2","4"],
    "currentPrice":"8,000",
    "answer":"3"
  },
  {
    "question":"What do the British and Americans celebrate on the 4th Thursday of November?",
    "variants":["Christmas","Mom's Day","Thanksgiving Day","Dad's day"],
    "currentPrice":"16,000",
    "answer":"Thanksgiving Day"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the main and deepest river in Britain?",
    "variants":["Seine","Mississippi","Volga","Thames"],
    "currentPrice":"32,000",
    "answer":"Thames"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is Scotland called?",
    "variants":["Country of mountains","Land of lakes","Land of songs","Country of rivers"],
    "currentPrice":"64,000",
    "answer":"Country of mountains"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the symbol of England?",
    "variants":["Rose","Narcissus","Tulip","Gladiolus"],
    "currentPrice":"125,000",
    "answer":"Rose"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the largest state in the United States?",
    "variants":["Florida","Alaska","Texas","California"],
    "currentPrice":"250,000",
    "answer":"Alaska"
  },
  {
    "question":"In what year did the Battle of Kulikovo take place?",
    "variants":["1380","1569","1616","1773"],
    "currentPrice":"500,000",
    "answer":"1380"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the name of the deepest point on the Earth's surface, located at the bottom of the Mariana Trench?",
    "variants":["Philippine","Abyss Challenger","Kermadec","Black Lair"],
    "currentPrice":"1,000,000",
    "answer":"Abyss Challenger"
  }
]